（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
- 问答任务中的后处理操作。
- The post-processing step in a question answering task.
在做问答任务时，
When doing question answering,
初始数据集的处理
the processing of the initial dataset
意味着以多个特征拆分示例，
implies splitting examples in several features,
其中可能包含也可能不包含答案。
which may or may not contain the answer.
由于我们的标签是词元的索引
Passing those features through the model
其对应于答案的起始和结束，
will give us logits for the start and end positions,
通过模型传递这些特征
since our labels are the indices of the token
将为我们提供开始和结束位置的 logits。
that correspond to the start and end the answer.
然后我们必须以某种方式将这些 logits 转换为答案，
We must then somehow convert those logits into an answer,
然后从每个特征给出的各种答案中选择一个
and then pick one of the various answers each feature gives
作为给定示例的答案。
to be the answer for a given example.
对于处理步骤，
For the processing step,
你可以参考下面链接的视频。
you should refer to the video linked below.
验证方面也没有太大的变化，
It's not very different for validation,
我们只需要添加几行来跟踪两件事。
we just need to add a few lines to keep track of two things.
我们保留 offset mapping，而不是丢弃它们，
Instead of discarding the offset mappings, we keep them,
并且通过设置特殊词元的偏移量
and also include in them
以及将问题设置为 None
the information of where the context is
将所保留的 offset mapping
by setting the offsets of the special tokens
包含在上下文的信息里。
and the question to None.
然后我们还跟踪每个特征的示例 ID，
Then we also keep track of the example ID for each feature,
能够将特征映射回
to be able to map back feature
他们初始的例子。
to the examples that they originated from.
如果你不想计算验证损失，
If you don't want to compute the validation loss,
你不需要包含所有这些
you won't need to include all the special code
用来创建标签的特殊代码。
that we used to create the labels.
完成后，我们可以调用 map 方法
With this done, we can apply that preprocessing function
应用该预处理功能。
using the map method.
我们采用 SQUAD 数据集
We take the SQUAD dataset
就和问答视频的预处理中所用到的一样。
like in the preprocessing for question-answering video.
一旦完成，下一步就是创建我们的模型。
Once this is done, the next step is to create our model.
我们在这里的问答管道背后
We use the default model
使用默认模型，
behind the question-answering pipeline here,
但你应该使用你想要评估的任何模型。
but you should use any model you want to evaluate.
我们将运行一个手动评估循环，
We'll run a manual evaluation loop,
所以我们用我们的特性创建了一个 PyTorch DataLoader。
so we create a PyTorch DataLoader with our features.
有了它，我们可以使用标准的 PyTorch 评估循环
With it, we can compute and gather
来计算和收集所有
all the start and end logits like this,
像这样的开始和结束的 logits。
with a standard PyTorch evaluation loop.
完成后，我们就可以真正深入到后期处理中了。
With this done, we can really dive into the post-processing.
首先，我们需要一张从示例到功能的映射，
First, we'll need a map from example to features,
我们像这样创建。
which we can create like this.
现在，对于后处理的主要部分，
Now, for the main part of the post-processing,
让我们看看如何从 logits 中提取答案。
let's see how to extract an answer from the logits.
我们可以针对开始和结束 logits
We could just take the best index
只取最好的索引，
for the start and end logits and be done,
但如果我们的模型预测得出了不可思议的结果，
but if our model predicts something impossible,
就像问题中的标记，
like tokens in the question,
我们将查看更多的 logits。
we'll look at more of the logits.
请注意，在问答管道中，
Note that in the question-answering pipeline,
我们基于概率将分数归因
we attributed score to each answer
于每个答案，
based on the probabilities,
我们这里没有计算。
which we did not compute here.
就 logits 而言，我们在分数中的乘法
In terms of logits, the multiplication we had in the scores
成为加法。
becomes an addition.
要快速完成，
To go fast,
我们不会查看所有可能的开始和结束的 logits，
we don't look at all possible start and end logits,
仅需最好的 20 个就足够了。
but the 20 best one is enough.
我们忽略产生不可能答案和答案太长
We ignore the logits that spawn impossible answers
的 logits。
or answer that are too long.
正如我们在预处理中看到的，标签 0,0
As we saw in the preprocessing, the labels 0,0
对应无答案。
correspond to a no answer.
否则我们使用偏移量
Otherwise we use the offsets
在上下文中得到答案。
to get the answer inside the context.
我们来看看对于第一个特征
Let's have a look at the predicted answer
预测的答案，
for the first feature,
这是得分最高的答案
which is the answer with the best score
或最好的 logit 分数
or the best logit score
因为 SoftMax 是递增函数。
since the SoftMax is an increasing function.
这个模型就是合适的。
The model got it right.
接下来我们只需要为每个例子循环这个，
Next we just have to loop this for every example,
在示例生成的所有特征中
picking for each the answer with the best logit score
选择具有最佳 logit 分数的答案。
in all the features the example generated.
现在你知道如何从模型预测中获得答案了。
Now you know how to get answers from your model prediction.
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)